{
    "id": "c887017da964463492ca8bea86a67e7e",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Air conditioning …………………………. for a comfortable house.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "is making",
                "makes",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0967d35795324577bf51bef1abd89d2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The new hospital ……………………………… in the coming year.",
            "description": "To express simple futurity, we use the simple future. The passive form is used here because the subject is not the doer of the action.",
            "answers": [
                "will build",
                "will be built",
                "would be built"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f6011d55cc954a8ba43989339b35329a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dancing ………………………….. right after the dinner",
            "description": "To express simple futurity, we use the simple future.",
            "answers": [
                "will commence",
                "will be commencing",
                "is commencing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5bb039aa6eb3429e83a6810706389cea"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I went to his place yesterday, his wife ………………………….. me a cold reception.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to talk about finished events in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "gives",
                "gave",
                "has given"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24295be90feb4f67b8c8382ccf6fa822"
        },
        {
            "question": "My birthday …………………………….. with my wedding anniversary.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is coinciding",
                "coincides",
                "coincide"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "42a0b06c19aa4e05841e53b4da2bd640"
        },
        {
            "question": "His parents ………………………… him because he was an only child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pampers",
                "has pampered",
                "pampered"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "93c17140d2184f4999da8d2151c71cb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "In hemophilia the blood ………………………. properly.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "does not clot",
                "do not clot",
                "not clot"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f3909e3735cc491fa0766761bd28c9cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Pine trees …………………………. to the ever green class.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "belong",
                "belonging",
                "are belonging"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "17a03b7040a049f2b742d46c2299ace8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The class ……………………………. graduating in June.",
            "description": "Collective nouns are usually treated as singular.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3537d0627c6d41c5b95efc3dd56f937e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Eggs ………………………….. according to size.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "classify",
                "are classified",
                "have classified"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2284ff06f79c4e4c99f0353ba44217f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Butter …………………………. by churning cream.",
            "description": "The passive verb is used here because the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "is made",
                "has made"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "70a3ff92711a49b3b67cb269054a2fe6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The circuit of the earth around the sun …………………………… about a year.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "is taking",
                "takes",
                "has taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b0192be149840aab92c5bcb3fcec71a"
        }
    ]
}